woohoo how's it going hey great how are
you I'm doing good I wish we had like
five minutes to like get technical
difficulties but it doesn't allow you to
do that that's okay we're okay so are we
live right now yeah might
yeah so how like I went through the
videos because I was like you know went
through the embracer Kink's uh video and
I was like wow man that was such a long
time ago now yeah that was that was
amazing though you were there from the
beginning from the beginning yeah and
even then like you know when we when we
take Calgary you put Calgary in when you
take Calgary you put that into
perspective um it's like you were doing
something at that time that was
revolutionary you know in a in in a
sense that you you were pushing the
envelope when a lot of people around
that time were not really concerned
about you know natural and I think just
like I mean the whole
natural movement I think that was more
in uh I think that was more in the
United States and it was just and in
Calgary because Calgary is so
backwards you know having someone to
come from Toronto and really push that
envelope I thought that was amazing you
know what I mean and and now there was a
conference I was speaking at like a
black women's hair conference like you
had started something that grew to
something else right so you know amazing
amazing that's that is quite impactful
so uh we're gonna I'm just gonna do one
more push um I'm just gonna just put
this push and if you can share just say
hey I'm Live come on in and uh if no one
else comes in that's okay we're just
gonna get started um
anyway okay sounds there's a lot to talk
about I miss what you said there's a lot
of there's a lot to talk about lot
went oh wow we're gonna get you know I I
want to give you that a platform for us
to really truly discuss you know some
some some issues that are in the
community but you know also like
motivational things like I I I really
want to truly understand what is going
on in your mind and you know hopefully
we can inspire people in the
process so I sounds good sounds
good let's see if I can find it but we
do have K in the house and if you look
on your kente is a
uh uh is a friend of mine he does
podcasting and and and whatnot he's in
the movie industry
[Music]
nice to meet you K all about and um you
know we have a lot of online friends
that we've met on this platform called
lab and um they just recently closed
down so that's why we're using fire talk
and and I would I would highly suggest
you use the fire talk as well because I
think that um for the stuff that you're
doing uh you know Canada is such an echo
chamber I think that you you got to
spread that message beyond Canada and
get it out to the masses because I think
what you're doing is
phenomenal well you're amazing for
giving um people a platform in order to
share what their heart is all about and
what they want to do and how they want
to impact the world and the community so
I do those to you for
sure appreciate so we're gonna get uh
we're gonna get into it we have three
people in the room that's you me
Andante but that's okay uh let's first
start by um first tell us what you do
like who are
you who Am I who am I that's isn't that
like a loaded question who am I well as
you know my name is Denise Gordon I am a
daughter um I am a sister I am a person
who is passionate for um spiritual
things I love God I am a Christian I am
an entrepreneur I love to inspire other
people and I like to always uh Be
Inspired myself so I'm always looking
for a new and interesting opportunities
um a person who loves um natural hair
that was definitely why I um I focused
on doing that when I was in Calgary
someone who likes to um Empower others
to love themselves that's something that
um I'm very passionate about as well I'm
a person who loves education I'm a
student I am I am doing my Master's of
Social Work degree right now so that's
why I ended up leaving from Calgary to
come back to uh the GTA in order to uh
do my masters and I'm almost finished um
I'm a person that is passionate about
life um about love I am single at the
moment but I'm still passionate about it
and so I'm happy for other people um and
I'm always you know finding a way to
help people you know get to what they
want in life especially relationally um
yeah so that's just a little bit about
me that's kind of like a little question
but like yes I'm passionate about
business I'm a person who um
believes that you know it's okay if you
want to do the ninetto five everyone is
not the same but there are opportunities
out there I want to be the person to let
people know there's other option there's
other opportunities you don't all have
to be do the same thing you don't all
have to do the ninto five um there's
something something else out there so
you could push yourself beyond the
limits because um I don't only say that
in order to um tell people to do that
but I am doing that myself I'm doing
that little by little by little so as I
learn things I love to share it so
that's a little bit about me all right
so uh what do you do for
living what do I do for I am an
entrepreneur for a living that's not
exactly what I do um to get paid so
recently um so as I was saying before I
um I'm doing my Master's of Social Work
degree so I started that
2014 and so I'll be finished
2017 thank you Jesus can't wait till
that be over
right now I actually have like some
chapters to read because of an exam on
on Friday so everyone anyone who prays
you could go ahead and pray for me to do
that um but um yeah so that's so my f
I've always been in the social services
as I said before I love to help people
so that's where that um the desire to do
that degree and continue to do my
masters came from um I as I said before
I worked in social services so I work
with people um with brain injuries
mental health um behavioral issues um
issues with the law um different
marginalized groups and that's what I
was doing um for the most part before I
um started to focus more on my
entrepreneurial aspirations um and right
now in regards to my entrepreneurial
aspirations I'm in health and wellness
and I'm also in um just empowering
people to be able to find the
opportunities to gain wealth and to to
get wealth so that's what I I do right
now and so that's what's paying the
bills and that's what awesome I just
want to say hi to Mark profit uh the
author of predictive Innovation uh Mark
uh my girlfriend and I read the book
over the weekend and we we did we went
on the like we were on the like we used
the alternative grids to figure out the
next Innovation for blab and that was
actually a really good exercise like so
maybe we could reposition the book for
for couples you know for people that you
know are into um you know just building
things being entrepreneurs but I just
want to say uh hi to Mark um I'm going
to be going back and forth and
addressing people that are in the room
it's not necessarily A Ono many
conversation it's like you know I love
the interactivity of online streaming so
uh uh and it's it's awesome if we had
more people in the room you would see
how powerful that this platform is
okay so no problem I
okay that's amazing I didn't know that
you were an entrepreneur um I did do
some I was doing some research but I was
I I knew that you were in the mental
health uh Arena I actually my company
Bai creative we like from when we you
were one of our first uh like you know
we did some video work for you for
embrace your
kinks yes you did it was amazing I was
just looking at it just a little while
ago and I'm like oh my God so fun it was
nerve-wracking because I've never done
anything like that before but I was so I
felt so blessed that you um you know
took a chance on us and you really did
an awesome job like you was amazing
everyone who saw that video was very
pleased so yes if anyone needs videos
anyone needs anything to do with
electronics so when we when we started
like I I was just into like video and
did all that stuff but then the the the
the the um company migrated into m
Health uh and and to uh people with
disabilities for because every website
that we sell we donate a website to
entrepreneurs with disabilities it's a
disabilities empowerment program um so I
thought um normally I introduce myself
normally I say that that's the first
thing I say but we just jumped right
into embrace your kinks forgot to say
that but yeah folks if you guys know
anyone that's in the community that
wants to be an entrepreneur and if you
want to empower them um get them to go
to my website I'll put the links uh in
the chat afterwards uh visit the website
we have a waiting list uh uh for people
so as soon as we sell a website we can
uh uh as soon as we sell a website they
are offered an opportunity to have their
own website for free and um if they want
to expedite it they just have to find a
sponsor or someone that wants a website
and then we can expedite that process as
well so anyway uh so you are you're
doing so much stuff right now but in
order for you to be who you are today I
want to know your story like so we have
all day and I want to know I want to
know like you know not just who you are
but like what is your story everybody
has a
story so start from the
beginning start oh goodness from the
beginning well on one day October 28th
uh
well that is my birthday um but yeah I
um grew up in the city of Toronto I was
born in Toronto and um two lovely
awesome awesome awesome parents um
everan Ling Gordon and I am the middle
child so I don't know I've heard many
different philosophies about U Middle
children but anyways I guess we'll see
if it's all true but yeah I have two um
older brothers and two younger brothers
so four brothers Al together I'm the
only girl right it's snap bad in the
middle and I grew up in Toronto um and
moved to miss Saga in um I think around
grade one and then I we moved to Bramton
about 13 or 14 years ago so and
then um as you know Al agree a few years
back 2011 and I returned
2014 but um you know who am I so as I
said before I grouped my parents are
from Jamaica they're born in Jamaica
they um moved to Canada for a better
life they wanted a better experience
they um grew up in uh pretty rough
conditions and um they they I guess that
both of them they decided that you know
what I'm gonna have children one day and
I do not want them to be born in what I
was born in my mom would always tell me
about stories of her walking to school
with no shoes playing outside with no
shoes being burnt by thear because she
has no Sho and different things like
that but um
she's she had defin they both definitely
have had humble beginnings and so I
would say that you know I came from
humble beginnings as well they were both
trying to make it in a new country um
and my dad was working they would tell
me how much they were working for an for
hour when they first came here and it's
kind of unbelievable um but yeah and so
pretty much what we grew up with we grew
up with love my parents love each other
and to this day they are together thank
God because that isely not um in
statistics um these days um but yeah
they're still together celebrating I
think is about 40 so years together
being married um and um right now
they're probably hanging out together
because you know they love each other
and so that they are an example to me
about love about marriage and what's
possible out there um but yeah they
definitely instilled um beliefs values
in us and culture um
they are passionate Christians they were
they both weren't born my dad was born
in a Christian household my mom wasn't
but as they continued to grow up they um
were able to find their own path and
they um became Christians and so I grew
up in a Christian household as I said
before very humble um very
strict very very very very strict um of
a very traditional but it was definitely
a house of love um as I said before I
have four Brothers they love to have fun
they love to tease me even till this day
they love to tease me but I know that I
am loved by my parents my brothers and
so we're very very close so sometimes
people look at us and wonder how come
you guys are so close how come you guys
spend so much um on the holidays like
for birthdays the siblings always get
together you know to go it's just a
tradition we go out to eat somewhere
nothing fancy nothing huge just go
together and laugh and that's what we do
for every person's birthday um we just I
just celebrated my brother's birthday
just the other day and now that um a
couple of them are married my two older
brothers are married um and one has
children they all come so the family or
the siblings are just getting bigger and
bigger and bigger hi princess Coco nice
to meet you I just I just saw
that welcome welome hey hey Coco how are
you
doing okay so so that's that's amazing
so you grew up in a really good
environment you know did when you say
that you that your parents were you know
they had humble beginnings did that
affect you you know what were your
thoughts on that like when you were
growing up like when when you look back
in time like how did all of that affect
you well you know what the interesting
thing is that I didn't know any better
so it's not like I knew I I you know I
would see people with a different
lifestyle and then me what was me right
I grew up you know we grew like regular
you know we grew up in the first we were
born in the um in an apartment building
so we went from apartment building to a
um what was it called like a not a condo
but like you know townhouse complex and
from townhouse complex to a um semi-
detached and from a semi- detached to a
detached home so like I guess we you
know went in stages and stages and
stages and we grew with that but um what
that taught me was to work hard to work
hard for what you need like they they
had no idea what life was going to be
like um wow like I went back to Jamaica
to um bury my uncle in January and I we
had the opportunity to go to the area or
the the house the actual house where my
my father was born and um we went to the
school that he went to for um Junior
High and all those different things they
had different um names for their
schooling but um I was definitely
brought to
tears um because the house that my dad
was they grew up ring like it was like
in the shambles but the thing that
brought me to tears even more was that
there was a family that were squatting
in that household like I heard it was
distant relatives um I didn't know who
they were but like there was no windows
the doors were kind of rickety
everything like I think there was like
from the different storms it tore it
down and when I went there and I saw a
little girl she was I don't know
teenager maybe 13 years old I began to
think wow that could have been me that
could be me right now in that house that
could have been me and that's what
brought me to tears and so every time
you know even though you know some
people might not even think where you
know I grew up from humble beginnings
because we had somewhere to live we
never had any issues of um being
homeless even though um you know my
parents we didn't have a lot of money
growing up we always had enough like
there was no time where we felt that we
had to go to bed hungry never like I
don't know maybe my parents could
probably you know tell me later on that
they went to bed hungry but I don't
think they did my dad was a hard hard
worker and now he's retired but he's
still working hard he's finding
something to do and my mom was an
amazing she was also a hard worker and a
homemaker um and so I didn't feel I
didn't feel the Brent of all that like I
felt I always felt loved I always felt
cherished I always felt um I always felt
cared for so but it help help me to
realize that you know what um I need to
continue to work for what I would like
work for what I need and continue to you
know that no matter what I want in life
I can achieve it because if my parents
when I saw where they came from they
were able to come here and so you know
now people might think oh my gosh you
know you're you know you live in this
house or whatever it might be you know
but that's not where they started so it
shows me that you know no matter where I
start continue to go further and further
and further because if my parents went
from that place where they grew up to
where they are now obviously it's my job
and my siblings job to go the next level
so that's why I've been more passionate
about business more passionate about
empowering other people to um become
financially free because um you know
it's like almost taking the Baton you
know now we're here I need to go to the
next level I need to be able to and also
bring others with me bring people from
my community people that look like me
people that don't even look like me but
bring other people along with me because
that's something that I also learned
like in our when I was younger kids used
to always come to our house they would
have come to get like Popsicles or
whatever because my parents were giving
and loving so that's something that's
also um a part of my life um you know
even though they they we you know we
didn't have everything I didn't have the
brand name stuff I didn't have like you
know the Nikes or whatever I kind of got
I think I got FAS one day but it was a
t-shirt um for those who don't even know
who that is what that is yeah it was
like a brand um and but you know that
didn't that that didn't bother me
because my my family we weren't
materialistic so that didn't even I
didn't even realize what that was about
until like later on when I um got to
meet other people but yeah it just
helped me to you know appreciate
everything that I have appreciate where
I am feel blessed every day that I could
be in a different situation but I'm not
and that there's so much more out there
for me to experience and to attain so
that's that's that's pretty awesome I
think that um oh I hear an echo you do
you have headphones by any
chance I do but um I would have to go
downstairs to get do do you need me to
go get it I could um yeah if you if if
it's not if it's if it's not too much of
a hassle otherwise you if you turn down
the uh the volume um there won't be an
echo um okay so let me try how does that
does that work if that doesn't work I
can go ahead and get it testing testing
testing testing okay I'm good I'm good
you sure yeah okay I can go and get it
if you want no we're good okay okay so
uh it's an amazing story because like
you know in and I can only I'm in the
black community obviously because I'm
black and um you know the one the one
thing that that I that we notice in the
black communities that we don't we're
not a lot of us are in homes we're two
parents are available to assist so what
are your thoughts about that like two
parent home you know struggling together
uh did you ever witness you know you
don't have to you can divulge as much as
you like but did you did you ever
witness your parents in like turmoil
with each other and how did they over
overcome those situations and if there
wasn't any turmoil then you know how did
they keep the the relationship going so
that you and your your your siblings
could
Thrive yes so um you know what to be
honest every there's you know within
relationships there's always turmoil um
if there's no turmoil some things some
someone is not being heard that's what
I've come to learn I'm not a
relationship expert maybe one day I will
be but um you know like um within
relationships it's always termo it's
always something people have opinions
people have um attitudes people even
though that you know people might have
been you know might have grown up in the
same country they've had different
parents different you know ways of
culture in the household so yes
definitely you're asking me if I've ever
seen any kind of termal or or um tension
between my parents yes like um I can't
say it was like you know overwhelming it
was just for me I guess it was normal
you know they would might they might
disagree on something and then I would
know that they're disagreeing up on
something but the amazing thing as
you're talking about um how do they get
over it or how do they deal with it
first of all um it goes back to their
relationship with Christ um they both
were they both believed in marriage they
both believed that marriage is forever
they both believe that um they were
brought together for a purpose they also
wanted to always make sure that they are
being an example to
us um and um that was I think that was
what was what
um help them throughout whatever torm
Ral they might have been through um
there's been so many so many so many
relationships that I don't know what the
statistics are right now like it's kind
of sad I don't even know if I want to
repeat it but the statistics are
horrible Some Mo a lot of the times you
know relationships don't even start off
as a two parent household they're
probably you know you know different a
different lifestyle but um you know and
then when they are married you know
after the maybe after children or after
things happen in life people break up
but um thank God there was never a time
where you know where that happened in my
household um that is a blessing that is
something that I can't you know not
everyone could say and so um you know I
guess it's an anomaly in the this day
and age right but yeah they had a very
the very very strong um belief and Um
passion for Christ and for and a belief
in marriage and staying
together and yes they fought yes they
argued but they came back together
literally through prayer and through
communication and that's another thing
too like um Communications is key no
matter what your um your your particular
beliefs are communication is key and so
um no matter you know might have it
might have taken like hours might have
taken a day or whatever might have taken
um you know they came back together
through communication um and then of
course I believe you know there's
probably way more things that I didn't
see because a lot of times things happen
behind closed doors conversation
happened behind closed doors and I think
as parents they did a great job in in
shielding because um they weren't always
up in our face oh look at this what's
going on you know it was just you know
you'd see you'd see some you know you
just know something's a little bit
off yeah the LA the jokes are not
happening as you know frequent as before
and all that stuff but um you know they
did they always came back together they
always um you know knew it was important
to come back together because you know
that's another amazing thing like they
like two peas in the pod like like when
one's going out they're like do you want
to come with me oh no you know whatever
they are doing my dad's out in the
garden my mom my dad's like come with me
like you know so I think after being
together for so long they're like best
buds too so that's another thing that's
important for relationships they're like
friend they're best friends exactly they
could I've seen them laugh together I've
seen them cry together I seen them
through all these different amazing
amazing emotions but it was together and
so I think that's what another thing too
together they want to do it together
they struggle together they they you
know getting you know their first
mortgage together having you know
dealing with not having jobs together
but it wasn't like well you better get
your act together and I'll you know
there it's always together and so
there's always together yeah together is
very very key yeah so I I just want to
uh say hi to everyone in the room uh we
have YC helard that just graduated from
uh Community Rehabilitation uh uh uh in
University of Calgary so she's in the
similar field as you uh Denise I want to
say hi to kente kente uh uh he was in
here earlier Soo Steph is in the house
uh what's up Stephanie H what's up prin
Coco if you guys have any questions for
Denise or if you want to add to the
conversation uh feel free to do so uh we
will have be having an open seat where
you guys can hop in and we can have some
discussions we're yet to touch this you
know uh touch the topics um um to the
reason why Denise is here but you know
it's really good to understand the
foundation before we move forward into
those uh other the conversations so I
want to talk to you now my question to
you now is that you've had a great life
you've you've you've your parents came
from humble
beginnings you um and you've always had
love around you and community and
spirituality but in your life what are
some of your challenges uh progressing
from childhood to adulthood
um what what what what comes to mind um
when you think of challenges in your
personal
life um challenges in my personal life
so like one you know being a
female that could be like a challenge in
itself um or you know I can't I don't
know if I could say female but being for
me I'm a female so being a female speak
from your like you know from you know
not in a general sense but speak from
your sense like how has CH like you know
how were you affected by challenges what
were some challenges um that were in uh
that were in your way that you've either
learned um to overcome or you're still
overcoming like what got you here as
Denise
today yeah so as I say before being
being a female um there's you know
there's different um things that tends
to come with that but for me um there's
that whole confidence or lack thereof um
I grew up um you know I I was always
being told that you know you're
beautiful oh you're pretty or this and
that or you're cute or whatever and you
know I didn't actually um accept that
for myself I'm not sure what that what
was blocking that in my life um but that
was something that I had to deal with
like um I didn't yeah I wasn't always I
was very shy and I I still think I am
pretty shy um but I was very shy so I
didn't talk much and so um because of
that sometimes people would you know
take advantage of me take advantage of
that take advantage of my shyness and
quietness and all those different things
um so that's something I definitely had
to deal with um I had to be able to you
know be confident in speaking even
speaking like I always felt that I was
not eloquent I don't know I just like
there's other people who were able to
you know speak better and to be eloquent
and all those different things and so um
to even do public speaking oh my
goodness that was like that was
nerve-wracking for me like I always
thought well I don't know what am I
gonna say what am I you know I don't
have anything to say what am I gonna say
no one wants to hear what I have to say
and that probably stems back into the
lack of confidence that I grew up with
and so that's something that I've
actually been thinking about not too
long ago I was thinking where did that
come from because it didn't really come
from my family or my parents you know
they were very encouraging wanting the
best for us wanted us to shoot for the
star different things but I think that
was an internal battle that um I I've
had to deal with um and then on top of
that um from a very young age I recall
um having issues with um education so
I'm as I said before my parents were
born in Jamaica I was born in Canada um
but yet so I guess a mixture of I don't
know if it was racism or or
discrimination to a certain extent but
when I was um in you know U primary
school there were some issues with um
education um I had problems with um um
racism I would say with my teacher I I
recall he would always ask me questions
about my skin and why do your why does
your hand look like that why is your why
is why is one side of your hand look
like this and why is it so dark on the
outside and you know when I was younger
I didn't know what I didn't understand
because I think I don't know if I was in
grade like two or three but like there
wer at that time there weren wasn't a
lot of diversity where I grew up now
it's oh my gosh extremely diverse um in
Molton I grew up in Molton that's where
I went to um for people who are from the
GTA that's where I um I did a lot I grew
up um and yeah so this the teachers were
predominantly were from the dominant
culture or dominant um
race and um and he would ask me those
things and so I would start to wonder
about that like why do I look like that
why am I not like other people and those
things began to like I guess maybe
that's probably some of the things that
um began to play play on my psyche on on
my confidence and all that stuff because
you know he and then after that I was he
was he would put like I would be put in
a different class because they would
think that I wasn't learning as well and
because I'm from a different culture you
know as I said before um I I you know
there was not a lot of ders diversity
and um they would think you know they
would put me in a box because I looked
different I had a different skin
complexion compared to everyone else in
the class and so those so you saying
they put you in a different they put you
in a different class or they just put
you in different did they try to
segregate you from the rest of the class
is that what you're I had to go to an
ESL class actually that's kind of like
crazy because English is my first
language and so I always wonder about
all the time like what was I doing in
that class because I grew up in Toronto
and you know even like um you know the
fact my parents are Jamaican never
encouraged us to like even speak pwa so
I'm learning how to do that now so um
those are some things I had to De with
like I was in the E class with other
students that were not even born in
Canada I don't know why I was there um I
didn't have problems speaking English
but those are different things at
different that were um placed on me and
so in regards to my um idea of where I
would go educationally I would think
like well maybe maybe I can't do as much
maybe I maybe you know something's wrong
like you know maybe I can't go any
further than you know where the box that
I was placed in um by my teachers you
know by you know my experience and that
was Primary
School what would you tell the little
girl what would you tell the little girl
um that was you you know like what would
you tell your your
yourself if you had a chance to go back
and you know because I I you know
sometimes kids don't really understand
the what's going on in their
environments they just kind of go
through the the phases but what would
you tell the little girl now I would
tell that little girl you are beautiful
you are special you are unique there's
no one in this world that can do what
you can do so go ahead and do it I would
tell that little girl that people might
not be a might not understand you people
not might not accept you but guess what
you are loved you are precious go ahead
and reach for the stars and Beyond I
will tell that little
girl keep going you can do it don't
listen to the
naysayers you are smart you are
intelligent you can do anything you
could put your mind to
go ahead and do
it awesome that's wow that that kind of
that gives me goosebumps you know
because and and are you saying that
that's what you lacked did you were you
missing that
validation um that reassurance that you
were smart that uh that you were
beautiful you know being in because I in
Canada there's a lot of people here from
the states I want to say hi to court
place
um there's a lot of people that are from
the United States and and a lot of them
that live in Black communities so they
don't understand you know how as
Canadians how we grew up we were
probably one or two uh black uh people
in a classroom full of white people and
um so do you think that you were lacking
that just in general um did your parents
make you feel like did they say you were
beautiful did they give you that
positive reinforcement or you know did
you internalize what was happening in
school I know there's many questions but
like you know yeah go ahead and and and
answer okay I'll try to I'll try to
answer that question yeah like my
parents and and that's an interesting
thing that I have to like always tell
myself as well you they have gone so far
compared to where their parents grew up
like I don't know for those who are grew
up in a Caribbean um households um
especially back in the days um it's a
different it's a different type of um
Dynamic especially like you know what
kids were allowed to see and what
parents did in front of their kids um my
parents would tell me stories about the
fact that they never saw like their
parents you know hug and show that
affection unless they were joking you
know unless it was a jokey way like come
over here give me a kiss but more like a
joke it wasn't very you know that whole
loving you know loving way on a regular
basis and so even the words I love you
was something that they didn't hear so I
always have to realize that for them
whatever they did is they didn't even
experience that themselves like they
experienced the fact that their parents
were hard workers they that they took
care of their home no matter what they
went they were able to eat something
whatever if it was just you know some
yam and dumpling with a little bit of
you know sauce or something they were
able to eat something um but you know
that whole love and affection
affirmation um validation that was that
was not in their scope of what needs to
happen for the children the children
they were they talk you know children
need to go you know need to go to school
or do what do what they're told and
that's it right they have lots of
children in order to make sure the
household goes well and so my parents
they they definitely took Leaps and
Bounds like you know compared to where
their parents were so yes they they
definitely I know they definitely made
the effort to like you know always
encourage us they always wanted us to do
the best that we can do they always and
they never said you know what just go do
this you know go just do this part do
this you know program you know you can't
do this but always encourage um all of
us and and me as well to go further to
go further continue even like with
education now that I'm doing my masters
they've always been saying oh aren't you
gonna go you know do you want to
continue to go in school do you want to
do something more so they've always
encouraged us they've always told me
that I can do it and all that stuff so
but like I guess me more going back to
like my school um and my experience
growing up yeah like I was different and
so even the fact that I have my hair
natural that's an amazing thing because
um when I was younger it was always like
oh my God I can't wait till I'm old
enough to get my hair firmed oh my gosh
I want to be I want to look like the
other people that's what you know that's
what what's considered beautiful I would
see TV and I didn't see people like me
so that's you know I would think okay
well I would make a logic you know
logical um thought that you know what
that's what my goal should be being a
certain size being a certain uh skin
complexion having straight hair um and
and that was definitely not me you know
so I think that also played into my
psyche of what was possible for me um
you know and also in regards to
education I didn't I didn't really have
like mentors I didn't have anybody um to
to grow up to or to Aspire to be
because family um members have gone you
know at that time when I was younger not
a lot of family members were you know
educated second School much less High um
much less college or university much
less on further from that right so um
you know my scope of what my I guess the
limits that were I guess could have been
placed on me was through due to society
due due to what I thought was possible
and um that probably plagued into um
some insecurities or things like that
and so um I would you know be compared
to other people by I would do that I
would do I would take you know take on
that job to compare myself to other
people people would take on that job as
well and they would ask me questions
about like my hair why does your hair
look like that why you know why you know
why do you know different things and why
does your skin look like that and and
then I would wonder myself too like yeah
why do I look like that and so that
continued to plague you know into who I
was and as I was talking about um the
natural hair piece or the getting um my
hair permed I couldn't wait because at
least if I got my hair permed I would be
closer to what the
standard of beauty was and that's
exactly that's what I wanted that you
know that's and as as a little girl
everyone wants to feel you know all
little girls want to feel beautiful
every little girl wants to you know that
people like them and all those different
things so yeah so definitely um some of
what I experienced younger um affected
the way I thought about myself right so
now uh you've made leap some bounds in
terms of encouraging women and uh you
know encouraging yourself because well
how I stumbled you know I've known you
but I have i' I've known you in a sense
of hair and I've always had it in my
head that you know that you were you
know doing embracer I didn't know that
you were I thought you were still in
Calgary
and like we haven't talked like I was
doing the obsidian Awards and I seen you
there a few times um but uh I didn't
know uh what what you were up to and
then I started seeing your your Facebook
lives
and the first the first thing I noticed
I'm like holy cow she looks completely
different your parents so you you know
you lost you lost a little bit of weight
and you not only was that that's not
what I noticed it was the
message the message was you were like
you know being here you know when I met
you for the first time and you know
having those conversations with me you
know I feel like the person that I met
even though I didn't know you that well
uh I feel like the person that I I'm
seeing now through your Facebook live
they're kind they're two different
people or maybe you you're just I think
that this this person that I seen is
sharp and just about achieving
excellence and not that you weren't that
way before but what I notic hey it's a
growing process as personal development
that's okay it wasn't where I wanted to
I'm not where I want to be right now but
I'm going I'm moving forward I just love
the message and I watched your video and
you were just like it motiv it like you
you inspired me you know you inspired me
to go and take out the weights and
because you said you know what you know
like you just pick up you know just do
something it doesn't have to be you
don't have to go to the Mountaintop you
could take make little choices every day
and you were talking about healthy
choices today you were talking about um
you know that 20% is just physical
health and that you know the rest is
about eating healthy and you're on this
working out binge you're G do this
every you called it a binge yeah
yes so you're you're in it you're you're
100% so let's talk about health when we
think of and I wan to I want to add a a
spin to this like um when you think of
health and black lives you know we've
we've seen black lives matter um in a
sense of social justice against the
police and the communities but you know
black lives matter also within our
communities in terms of our relationship
sh with each other but the relationship
with ourselves yes so when you think
black lives
matter and you think Health what comes
to your
mind oh I think we're
Frozen Denise are you still
there uh we're gonna have to get you to
refresh if you could still see
me or am I
Frozen okay didies if you can see us
please
refresh I'm gon to boot you out the seat
I'm G to bring you back in
uh okay let's uh get her back let's get
her back in how folks how are you guys
liking the show so
far oh thank you
Coco yeah she's a remarkable person I I
love her story um you know and it's even
refreshing to hear kids that have been
brought up in a two- parent home and
witness people you know W you know like
here you have kids witnessing their
parents you know being the the
foundation I think it's just a beautiful
story so she's back uh you know
everyone's enjoying the conversation so
far uh so yeah let's uh get back into it
so black lives matter and
health what comes to your mind when you
when you when you hear those two phrases
yeah so um those say yeah black lives
matter and health I think that um that
is a holistic question question health
is I don't think it's just what you eat
just the exercise I think it's a mental
situation it's a spiritual situation
it's culturally okay and so I think that
there's a need to um to affect all those
particular areas in a black life um as I
was sharing some of my experience
growing up in you know black skin
there's a lot that um I could I didn't
get to experience I didn't see a lot of
mentors I didn't have a lot of people
bringing back or or taking it back to
our my community to show me that there
is more for me you know I was you know
my there's a limit place on Me based on
my surroundings based on the people who
were my superiors or people who I looked
up to um as educational figures um but
like in regards to Black lives and
health I think there is such a need for
that that
information to be propagated in our
community it's so sad to see so many um
people in from our community who are
sick from diseases that can be dealt
with um with eating differently with
walking a little bit longer with you
know taking the stairs instead of the
elevator a lot of what we our community
is dealing with can be dealt with
because with with
education and with this education it
could take make a difference in so many
communities and um also in
regards to health um so many people are
dying Too Young Too Young Too Young Too
Young with decisions decision that could
have been made like years ago years ago
that could affect their future so I just
think it's such an important um thing
for there to be um Role Models health
and fitness role model in our
community and definitely with the whole
with the black lives matter um Mantra
BEC into our community specifically to
deal with the health issues and all
those different things and deal with
what's important physically and Fitness
and Nutrition um there needs to be more
of um those particular role models and
mentors rising up in our community to
show that their way
of oh again we got a call get you back
it seems like your internet connection
um is starting to diminish so I'm GNA
get you to uh refresh your screen
Denise and
um uh
once you refresh just type in the chat
that you've refreshed and I'm going to
let you back in uh so folks uh I I
really I'm just adoring the the
conversation I I think that U what she's
saying about health is so true it you
know health is a holistic you know I
think that the health of the community
you know we're thinking black lives
matter um and you know we're trying to
empower ourselves to be uh for us not to
be the targets of police brutality Etc
however you know in order for our
leaders order for us to have leaders in
order for us to have a strong Community
we also need to have health you know to
focus on and that the types of foods
that we we need to be more conscious
about those sort of things and um you
know so I think that um oh I think she
should be back pretty soon here hey Rev
how's it
going so yeah like wow I but you know
health is such a like you know it's like
it just starts because you know you can
you can have you can have the
aspirations for wealth but what is
wealth when you don't have
health what is money when you can't
afford to yeah I'm glad to be here
too glad to I'm glad to be on here like
man blab was so shaky and you know I I'm
getting used to this fire talk business
here so I think Denise is back but yeah
you know so it's temporary if you so in
order for us to build our communities we
need to start motivating each other and
you know it's sad but I have to say that
you know I don't really see many
motivational you know like not that I'm
not aware of inspirational people but I
don't see many women that are are are
really FOC many black women that are
focusing on
motivational or focusing on health and
you know that's why I was so like you
know I gravitated towards Denise because
it was like wow it's not even like I've
seen women do that I've seen women get
into bodybuilding Etc uh but to have a
friend
you know show me that you know I can do
it that had that had that much more
impact on me than it would be if I saw
someone that I did not
know
so I think that um you know like this
like what you said in terms of health um
is is amazing so going back to uh uh
some of the questions here my question
to you is like why did you start
focusing on health like what was the
thing that sparked your um what sparked
your the motivation to to change your
lifestyle for sure for sure so
um I've always been interested in health
and wellness um when I grew up in junior
high I was always on the sports teams I
I love my volleyball baseball basketball
when I was in high school I you know I
did the basb I I did all the sports um
soccer I just didn't do track and field
um but um and even when I was in
university I tried
football I don't even know why I try
that because I don't even know I don't
understand the sport but I was always
interested in health um health and
wellness I just was not um always
incorporating those things in my life um
and as I continued to grow I began to be
around other people who are interested
in health and I would try different
things I would try the raw food diet I
would try the try the um vegetarian diet
no
one and um
and someone wants to talk to me so um
yeah I was trying so many different
things and I said even I tried um juice
fasting I tried um you know I even tried
uh smoothie diets for like 41 days I
think I did that just before the the um
racing my Kinks event um and I to that
event I got the small I've been in like
I don't know my adult life before now
and um yeah so I've always been
interested in it but my issue has been
cons was been was consistency and that's
that's why right now I'm always saying
consistency consistency consistency cons
that's like my my song and um and so
what hap you're asking what what was a
catalyst to let to get me to this where
where I am right now so um I don't know
if there was what particular Catalyst
but like I know I I was always saying um
that um you know there's no there's no
reason for me like in regards to the
weight that I was there was no there was
no reason I had no excuse thank God I
was healthy like I didn't have any kind
of health issues or anything like that I
you know there's different things that
are in my family line but um thank God
that it wasn't something that affected
me but like physically I thought you
know why am I this weight you know um
even when I was doing you know Sports in
school um I was never skinny I'm still
not skinny but like you know I was never
very you know that athletic figure I was
always active but never I never had a
certain physique that I was looking for
and so as I continued to get older and
um have different life experiences and
all those different things I would go up
and down in my weight but I've never I
never went past a certain you know
threshold like you know always people
who knew me have always um knew me as
being a person who was much um much uh
much chubbier you know and so what ended
up happening was I think there was one
day when I was like checking my blood
pressure and just because like I was
doing with my family I was like oh let
me let me try that let's see how that
goes and I did that and then the cuff
That was supposed to go on my
arm it didn't fit and I was I was upset
whoa and so like it it was able to get
on and I was able to it was like a you
know at home at home version and I was
just like I was shocked I was like
wondering what in the world just
happened
because I think like you know especially
when I moved back home I because I was
when I was living in Calgary I was on my
own so I I had to cook for myself and
all those different things I moved back
home I was comfortable I started you
know school and so I was constantly you
know doing the whole late night thing
eating whatever and you know and then I
just I guess the weight creeped up even
further so at that time I was at the
highest weight that I could recall being
and I was just like
wow I I was I was shocked because I was
was like well I never really saw myself
as you know being that big I was always
I was never skinny but I always you know
put myself together and all those
different things so that was never
really a concern of you know being
beautiful or anything like that but I
wonder when I saw that I was like why is
that not fitting why is that why am I
struggling to put it on and then I
realized I need to do something I had no
excuse for being the weight that I was
um you know I didn't have children I
didn't have any kind of me you know any
kind of Health um issues why was I that
weight so um and I realized that you
know weight is usually associated with
different kind of ailments and so you
know what I knew that I wanted to live a
long life I wanted to be able to live a
long life for when I do have children to
be able to like be active with them and
to be able to um show them the right way
of living and so I want to be an example
before they even came on the scene I and
I also want to be an example to people
that I knew I I have a lot of different
friends from different areas of life and
I also want to be an example I don't
think I was thinking about being an
example to anyone else at that time but
as I continue to go on that particular
journey I realized that I was being a
example and then I that even propelled
me to continue on and so that was pretty
much what it was I I realized that there
was no excuse for where I was I've
always wanted I've always been
struggling with health and not Health
but like um weight I've always been
heavier but I've always wanted to get to
a certain weight and I just said into my
mind I need to do this there's no excuse
so let's do it and that's that what
propelled me and I started this
particular Journey um January um January
14th actually
2015 so it's been a little over a year
and um consistency is key in order to
keep the m to in order to maintain
everything as well hello
yeah I hear EO just like the the volumes
fluctuate so sometimes it's like it
tries to pick up background noise let me
Che
further is it better
now yeah it's better so yeah I I had an
epiphany maybe four years ago I was uh
at the mall with my son I was over 200
pounds and um just for a little bit
there I was just you know working late
nights and hopping into McDonald's and
eating fast food at the the you know in
the malls and stuff and you know I went
to the the mall and I remember I could
not bend over to tie my shoes and as
that was
like my God what's going on you know so
and then I and then and I look up and
then there's this guy my my friend uh
you know I forget his name Kon he worked
at this uh um he was working at this uh
um World Health and I just bumped into
it afterwards and I here I am
still you know breathing heavy from like
and it was so embarrass bassing that you
know I was with my son I could have bend
over and time my shoes so you know that
that whole realization that and I I I
was able to keep off the weight and I
kind of kept you know like Foods I was
eating to minimum but I resonate with
you uh when it when it comes to finding
out that you can't do something that you
are normally accustomed of doing like
putting on you know like you want you
want to check your health but you can't
because the the the thing doesn't fit on
your arm so you know that that would
piss me off so for you to to get into
that you know to have that Epiphany and
now this is where you are and like I you
are inspirational because you know I
think that that some of the Americans
that are here they don't really
understand Canadian culture in terms of
like you know a lot of us are quite Meek
and we're very polite and when we take
sorry sorry so sorry I'm so
sorry yeah sorry sorry sorry sorry yeah
you know or thank you thank you thank
you you know and we we don't like to put
our business out on social media we
don't like to air it out and we talk
behind people black like girl you know
she's starting to work out um you
know I don't think she's gonna do it I
don't think she's you know like so all
this is happening within our communities
and you know in the Caribbean Community
the words are very harsh and the fact
that you went out of your way like what
made you throw this out online the
interesting thing um Ryan is that I
didn't frze out online very early in the
beginning like I said before um I
started January 14
2015 and I don't think I showed myself
um like I you know would have like old
pictures posting or whatever the last
picture I recall po having online was in
January like my dad's birthday was like
the 23rd or something like that and um
and that's probably like you know I
would like I would recycle old pictures
but I didn't when I was going through
the process I didn't put myself out
there at all and that's that's that's
another interesting thing because I kind
of I kept it to myself because first of
all there's people that's always doing
different things they're putting it out
there I see it all the time people are
posting things oh you know watch me lose
weight or watch me do this watch me you
know and especially you know January
everyone's doing a New Year's resolution
so I didn't want to be like just another
New Year's resolution girl because it
was January but um you know and I I kind
of kept it to myself like the only
people who actually knew what was
happening in my life were my family
members um and my friends because when
we would go out they would see what I
was what I was eating um and they would
wonder what in the world is she eating
and why is she eating that like what is
wrong with her um my family members were
worried about
me they're like always trying to feed me
because when they saw me losing the
weight they're like oh try some of this
you need to eat some more food or
whatever
um because that's another thing they
never saw me that way like all my life
as I said before I've always been chubby
and that was just I just thought that
was my my lot and everyone just you know
knew me that way and so um I didn't put
it out there because I don't know maybe
that I don't know why I didn't put out
there because I knew that I wanted to
share it eventually I felt that I wanted
to share it eventually but like I just
wanted to be able to do this it was more
so for me more so than anything else I
wanted to prove to myself more than
anybody else that I can do this that I
could accomplish it because as I said
before I tried the juice fasting I tried
the all these different types of um
eating to be healthy and all those
different things and they would go work
for like about you know a month 40
something days was the longest time and
then I would fall off the wagon and get
back to where I was gain more weight and
all those different things and so for me
I wanted to prove to myself that I can
do this so it wasn't about anybody else
it was about me at the beginning I just
wanted to say Denise you know what you
have this goal you've tried for years
and years and years it's been something
that you would write down on your you
know New Year's resolution or your
prayer list or whatever it is you want
to you know lose weight like I literally
wrote that down lose weight and I never
I never accomplish it and so when I when
I started to start putting it out there
was um I think maybe after I lost a
considerable amount of weight and I was
trying to actually I was doing a YouTube
video and so um for the YouTube video I
didn't like you know I I wanted to show
my hairstyle and so um you know during
the hairstyle video I did outside and so
the pictures were more of my body and so
people that's when people start to know
what's going on with me and everyone's
like some people are like Denise hey
they send me private messages oh my gosh
Denise you look different oh my gosh
who's that and all that stuff and so
that's when I began to say you know what
I cannot continue to keep this to myself
because there's people who need um
encouragement there's people who would
sent I I got messages from people that
you know they're like I've been trying
to you know lose weight for all this
time it's so amazing to see that you're
doing this and then I you know I I
almost began to get out of myself at
that time because um I realized it was
more than just about me getting to my
goals there are people who needed to
also get to their goals and um I I never
actually end up doing I was going to do
a before and after picture maybe one day
I'll share it with um you or or um
viewers um the before and after picture
but um before I even did that I just I
started to like talk about health talk
about wellness and
um and then afterwards um I just started
to put videos out there like I I
realized that there was this platform
that I could have used and I started
putting videos out there and um it was
amazing because then I started getting
awesome um encouragements people were
um I'm I'm like getting distracted you
see no no no we're this is this is the
culture like we like I I engage with the
the side Stat or the side panel and then
we engage so it's like an interactive
but there's usually in blab like the the
platform that we were on before
Oh you could like yeah you can click on
the pictures or click on the like the
your your face and then you get these
props so when you're saying things that
are really awesome you get you see these
like you know it's kind you know on
Facebook live how you get thumbs
up so I wanted to give you props but I
can't I'm like oh Lord I'm like tapping
the screen and I'm having some nostalgic
feelings thank you thank for that gift
oh thank you I do have a sweet
te um so but like you know the the
environment in these live chats is that
we engage like sometimes feel free even
to chat while while we're talking it it
just makes the people uh get to know you
more and makes them feel that they're
heard uh but anyway uh so as you were
saying yeah so yeah and then afterwards
um I started to like you know post more
pictures and then people were motivated
by the pictures that I posted and then I
would post more pictures and then
afterwards I joined um a Facebook group
for health and fitness and for working
out there' be like these five days
challenges and in this Fay challenge the
last challenge in order to get points
you had to actually post a video of you
doing one of the workouts and I was like
oh my gosh like people are going to see
me this workout like I'm not a
professional and so because I wanted the
points because I was
competitive I have a little bit of a
competive streak inside me not too big
but just a little bit um I wanted to get
my 10 points for that day so I posted a
video of me doing like you know the
Burpee challenge or whatever it was so
every day I would post a video in that
group um and then on the last day I had
to post a video for the entire Facebook
world so you know it's okay in the group
because you know there's just ladies in
the group trying to work out ladies who
were doing um you know their own workout
different things and so but then the
challenge was to post it to everyone in
like my whole entire Facebook group and
then you know I did it and I got amazing
feedback people were like saying great
job Denise oh my gosh you where did you
go Denise oh my gosh you look so
different then I realized okay there's
people who want to know what I'm doing
and then I started to as I continue to
you know realize you know it's not about
me I need to be able to like help
somebody else I need to be able to share
my experience with somebody else so that
someone else would realize that they can
do it as well that is not just you know
if you fall off the wagon you can get
back up again you could continue and you
could accomplish your goals you know
like sometimes setback setbacks happen
in our lives but you know what push
ahead you can go for it you can go and
you can accomplish goals and that's what
I realize and I I'm it's reinforced in
my life on a daily basis when I realize
I look at before pi pictures or even
today when I see people that I've um
haven't seen in the last year and a half
and they walk past me and you know I
would just be like are they being rude
or they really don't remember me and I
would just you know tap them on the
shoulder and I'll be like hi and they're
like looking at me like who hi and I'm
like it's Denise it's Denise Gordon and
they're like Denise Gordon who and I'm
like well and I try to say who my
parents are they're like what I don't
you know it's interesting because to me
I I still look like me but for people
outside they think I look like a toally
different person but that's okay but
yeah and now I'm on like Facebook live
and I go on Instagram um stories and I
post what I'm doing every day um I
started working out um another level
because before I was working but the
wagon so that goes to show you if you
fall off the wagon you can get back up
again um and now I I do like I jog and I
Sprint some sometimes and I walk in in
the morning and I start I started to
incorporate you know strength training
squats push-ups um you know burpees
whatever it is um in order to help to
build you know some muscle on my body to
help me going keep me going so yeah
that's that's what I do and and it's
amazing because um when I especially
when I did that Facebook live it wasn't
really about you know trying to get as
many people on to the the um that
particular live because it was late at
night no I didn't think and he was was
even awake like I was told my brother
was my brother came into my room and he
just said hey Dan um Facebook live is on
on we have it now our phone because I
have't I have a Samsung Galaxy um and we
didn't have it before and so he's like
you should do a Facebook live and I'm
like I don't have any makeup on I just
came from a meeting I'm too tired he's
like it doesn't matter he's like you
look good you could go ahead and do it
I'm like okay why don't you do he's like
no you go do it you go do it I have
encouraging siblings by the way I love
them all my brothers and my
sister-in-law they're very encouraging
and so I said you know what let me go
ahead and do it and then after that one
VI that first video people were actually
coming on and they were you know
encouraging me and they're like you know
wanting to know more about what I was
doing and I just contined to realize
okay there are people who need to hear
about what I have to say my experience
and um I also began to um say the same
thing that you know everyone has
something to say everyone has a mark to
place on the earth so go ahead and do
that
that's amazing I it's the top of the
hour it's actually 10 past um I'm over
the time limit here so uh yeah I I but I
want to thank you for for for coming in
and and how do you feel about being on
fire talk how was your first experience
on your this has been a great experience
like uh truthfully being transparent I
was like I'm I'm I'm excited but I'm
nervous I'm not sure what it's all about
and how it all works but um it's been a
great experience it's been a lot of fun
um as I said before I I kept on asking
so what do I need to do how do I prepare
and you're like just be there and I was
like okay but I like to prepare I like
to know what I'm going to go into but um
you made you made very easy very
comfortable and um it wasn't too scary
after
all yeah you know like I enjoy I enjoyed
your story um and how can um how can
people get a hold of you okay so I'm on
well my email is Denise H Gore
gmail.com so d n i s e h g o r d o
n gmail.com um on Instagram at Denise H
Gordon um please type it okay yeah yeah
Coco's asking I can't see if there's any
viewers in here but um I think that c
okay so um let me type it
so I wouldn't put your email address
just for security purposes but put your
um your other handles or links that you
want to to to post like you know if you
want people to add you to for sure okay
Instagram is
okay okay for
Instagram I'm on like a bunch of
different things so
Instagram I'm on Instagram at Denise H
Gordon um on Twitter at the same thing
Denise H Gordon I'm on Snapchat de3 so
um and this is also
Snapchat and YouTube I have YouTube
videos where I for the most part talk
about natural hair and natural hair care
and just my experiences in general um
and that is
um the
Hannah and what else is out there
Instagram Facebook you well my name is
quite common so there's a lot of Denise
Gordon on Facebook but um I think it's
Denise do Denise gordon. 752 I have to
put it in later on I can't remember
exactly what maybe I could find it right
here hold on oh here it is right here
I'll put my Facebook
up for those who want to are on Facebook
definitely friend
me that's my Facebook is it all there
could you you can see yeah that's that's
more than enough and um
folks before we head out I'm not sure if
there's people in the room or not
because it's saying that there's zero
viewers uh but I I highly doubt that
everyone just left um all at the same
time but um does anybody want to come in
on camera and and uh like you know let's
show Denise uh how how how we roll I'd
love to see how you
roll yeah so anyone in here that wants
to come in on camera like it just says
that everyone's offline for some reason
like it says user is offline Coco is
offline um yeah cuz I see princess Koko
right
there
yeah everybody's just gone I don't know
yeah because princess Coco said I'm here
so I'm not sure fire talk is haunted
by yeah fire is haunted by blab is
haunted by blab yeah no doubt no doubt
yeah this anybody want to ask any
questions before we go we'll have to
keep the the the like the anwers short
but the uh you know uh is there anything
you guys want to say or just want to
tell
Denise okay if not we're gonna there but
it's not it's not showing any viewers
are they able to still show their
picture oh thanks for having me Tashi
it's been a great
experience thank you and folks would you
guys come back oh sorry sorry I didn't
mean to
interrupt awesome oh thank
you how do you say o
OT it's why
whyat thank you appreciate
that yeah she's my partner in crme hi so
so why eat C helard so yes okay so we're
gonna we're gonna shut her down uh folks
I if you guys like this type of show
please type one if you guys will come
back again and and if you want to
encourage do you guys want to see more
videos or more fire talks like this uh
let me know because I will be looking
for people that are inspirational um and
bringing them aboard so type in one if
you you you want to see this uh um this
sort of show
again thank you wh see oh awesome thank
you C that's awesome you did a good you
did a good job to me so thank you so
much and um we are going to wrap it up
and um I folks I haven't figured out
what I'm going to call this segment I I
have the domain name the talking drum
uhca so I'm just thinking of different
things to call it and then it's just
going to be full production so uh I'll
keep you guys informed via social media
uh what I'm going to do um my name is
Ryan perz owner and founder of boai
creative uh we have a disabilities
empowerment program where we donate free
websites to entrepreneurs with
disabilities you can have uh either a
mental disability or you can have a uh a
physical disability uh the you know and
we're looking for for entrepreneurs that
are H are just new entrepreneurs that
are just starting out um that you know
that want to change their life they want
to become entrepreneurs uh so just keep
that in mind if you're like a a if
you're a rich entrepreneur you know
please do not apply because then you're
just uh you're you're preventing other
people from from from getting that
opportunity so I want to thank uh Denise
again uh for for coming to the show and
being brave and sharing um her nuggets
with the world you have her links please
add her because every day I get inspired
by the videos that she's posting and I
think uh Denise you have uh you you have
a long like a big career ahead of you if
you're going down this path and you
should like you know add as many people
as you possibly can get on fire talk and
bring this message to even to a another
level because there's so much women
around even North America that can
benefit from your from your message so
thank you very much thank you for having
me it's been a great experience um
you're an amazing host thank you for
making it um very comfortable a lot
easier than I thought it was going to be
you're amazing and all you awesome
wonderful viewers thank you thank you so
much for chiming in and also making me
feel welcome it's been great thank you
so
much okay thank you very much so
everyone um
uh the one takeaway in the show tonight
is that you're beautiful you know and
look at your children every day and just
remind them you're beautiful you're
worth it you know that that um don't let
anyone get in your way because as you
can see her parents were big they were
fundamental in her self-confidence and
wanting to push forward you know and you
know with that Foundation even if she ve
she had veered if she had veered off
into somewhere else she could always go
back to what she knows and that is just
being empowered and being herself so
again I want to thank Denise for hopping
in and hopefully you guys uh saw some
nuggets and and and got some takeaways
today so um I at 10:30 Mountain Standard
Time uh
12:30 uh 12:30 uh Eastern Standard time
I will be hosting the 1% jam session it
is always live it's a completely
different angle and different energy so
um those who who like that kind of stuff
motivational speaking and and whatnot
and having entrepreneurs uh you know uh
come together and discuss ideas uh that
show is definitely for you and you guys
can catch me at um
W.B creative.com and if you guys know
any anyone uh with a disability that you
know that could benefit from from um
from a program like what we what we
offer I'm going to post in the link in
description right now um and uh this is
our one love waiting list it's the
project is called one love and get them
to fill that out and they go on they
automatically get in you know put into
the waiting list uh so if there is a
website available for them uh we will
definitely call them and um and and
start the process so thank you guys so
much and uh much thank you